Nice to meet you.
Pleasure to meet you, sir.
Mandy, lovely to meet you.
So I would say that with Trump being anti-Constitution,
I don't really care, to be quite frankly.
Because in regards to the Constitution,
the Constitution is a document that should seek to serve us.
And when it fails to seek to serve us,
that can be amended.
Laws can be changed.
And quite frankly, the fact is, we're
defending things in this country that shouldn't be defended.
The First Amendment should not defend pornography
and making women and children be victimized
as a result of that.
I think things like blasphemy shouldn't be allowed,
per the First Amendment.
I think that quite frankly, there
are a lot of legal processes that
are enabling criminals and bad people
to fully enact their will in this country
in the name of the Constitution or following the Constitution.
So quite frankly, if Trump is anti-Constitution, good.
And I think he should go further.
So this is wonderfully revealing of the modern conservative
mindset, so I appreciate you spelling it out so openly.
Just checking, do you support the Second Amendment?
I do.
OK.
Surprise.
I was shocked to hear that.
I'm saying that Donald Trump is defying the First Amendment,
the Fourth Amendment, the Fifth Amendment, the 14th Amendment.
He's thinking of defying the 12th and 22nd Amendments.
You're saying you don't care about the Constitution,
but actually you do, because you quite like the Second Amendment.
You just don't like the bits that you disagree with.
Can I just be clear on that?
Yeah, absolutely.
OK.
How do you write?
I'm more than willing to amend it and include
the Second Amendment.
Whenever it's in your favor?
Yeah, absolutely.
Can Democrats do the same when they're in office?
No, absolutely not, because it's the friend and enemy.
So you don't believe in democracy?
No, I don't.
Absolutely not.
What do you believe in?
Autocracy.
By who?
Honestly, quite frankly, anyone who
is in line with Catholic teaching.
Donald Trump is not Catholic.
Of course he's not.
I completely agree, and that's part of the problem.
You don't support Trump?
No, I don't.
I didn't even vote for him.
I wrote in like John Pork or someone.
I can't even remember.
Why did you vote if you don't believe in democracy
and you want autocracy?
Well, because quite frankly, I voted.
This is fascinating.
I kind of voted just to stroll a little bit.
I came with this argument, but I'm bored of my own argument.
I'm much more interested in this.
So how do we get to an autocracy?
I think, quite frankly, that if we
are able to enact local leaders.
Who is the we, by the way?
I think, quite frankly, these far right conservatives
sitting right around me.
White people?
Yeah, absolutely.
So some of you guys, some of the people in this room
don't make the cut from what I can see visually.
Actually, hold on for a moment.
I do think that there are people who
happen to not be white who do actually
have history in this country and have roots in this country.
For instance, from the Mexican-American War,
we subsumed a lot of territory of people
who have far stakes in this country,
who happen to be Hispanic or what have you.
I'm for defending the traditional demographics
of this country, which is majority white.
It should stay that way.
How does the United States, I mean,
we've gone so off topic, but how does the United States
look like under your, sorry, what's your name?
My name is, well, my name's Connor.
It's a pleasure to meet you.
Took a little bit of a doubt there.
Oh, well, I use a pseudonym online, but fair enough.
How would Connor's America look?
What would it look like?
Well, quite frankly, I think we would deport people
who shouldn't be here.
I didn't ask about deporting.
What does the government look like?
Yeah.
I would say quite frankly,
it's under a sort of benevolent leader,
such as Franco. Where does he come from?
It could be a kind of aristocratic class,
could be someone who-
No, but who picks the autocrat?
Frankly, the people.
I mean, we could hold a vote on it.
Kings were paid-
So he's in that democracy?
Well, sure.
You can have a vote to get to that state.
And then no more votes afterwards?
Absolutely.
Wow. 100%.
Wow.
What if that autocrat kills you and your family?
You're fine with that?
Well, I'm not going to be a part of the group
that he kills because that's a whole thing.
How do you know?
Autocrats tend to kill everyone,
even their own supporters.
Carl Schmitt makes this point very well in his work.
It's the friend-enemy distinction, right?
You liberals-
Carl Schmitt, the Nazi theoretician?
Yeah, absolutely.
I don't care.
Are you a fan of the Nazis?
I frankly don't care being called a Nazi at all.
I didn't say that.
I didn't actually say that.
I said, are you a fan of the Nazis?
Well, they persecuted the church a little bit.
I'm not a fan of that, but-
What about the persecution of the Jews?
Well, I mean, I certainly don't support
anyone's human dignity being assaulted.
I'm a Catholic.
But you don't condemn Nazi persecution of the Jews?
I think that there was a little bit of persecution.
You may have to rename the show
because you're a little bit more
than a far-right Republican.